Guide to the George Washington University Publications collection, 1924-2017 RG0154
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- GW Student Journals, Series 10
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 12, No. 1), Autumn 1991; Series 10 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 13, No. 1), Fall 1992; Series 10 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 14, No. 1), Autumn 1993; Series 10 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 14, No. 2), Spring 1994; Series 10 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 15, No. 1), Autumn 1994; Series 10 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 15, No. 2), Spring 1995; Series 10 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 16, No. 1 &amp 2), Spring 1996; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 17, No. 1), Fall 1996; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 17, No. 2), Spring 1997; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 18, No. 1), Fall 1997; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 18, No. 2), Spring 1998; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 19, No. 1), Fall 1998; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 19, No. 2), Spring 1999; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 20, No. 1), Fall 1999; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 21, No. 2), Spring 2000; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 22, No. 1), Winter 2000; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 22, No. 2), Spring 2001; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 23, No. 1), Fall 2001; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 23, No. 2), Spring 2002; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The G.W. Review (Vol. 25, No. 21), Fall 2003; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Inquiry (Vol. 3), Spring 2006; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Kluchur 12 (Vol. 3, No. 12), Winter 1963; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The Potomac Review (Vol. 8, No. 1), Spring/Summer 1978; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Potomac Review (Vol. 8, No. 2), Fall 1979; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Potomac Review (No. 21), Spring/Summer 1981; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Potomac Review (No. 22-23), 1982.0; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - The Potomac Review (No. 24-25), 1983.0; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Potomac Review (No. 26-27), 1984-1985; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Capitol Economics Journal (Vol. I), 2021 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- GW Student Publications and Essays, Series 11
  - On Enobarbus, 1945; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The growth of plutocracy in colonial Virginia by Jessica P. Church., 1947; Series 11; ii, 32 leaves; 29 cm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Society of the Colonial Dames of America, Chapter III, prize essay at George Washington University, 1947.; Includes bibliographical references (leaves 31-32).
  - Steamboating on western rivers by Howard H. Borthwick., 1947-05-27; Series 11; iv, 56 leaves; 28 cm (Box 1, Folder 3)
    United Daughters of the Confederacy prize essay, 1947.; Includes bibliographical references (leaves 53-56).
  - The colonial agent: prize essay for the Colonial Dames prize (1948) by Chester James Byrns., Series 11; 10, [2] leaves; 29 cm. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Society of the Colonial Dames of America, Chapter III, prize essay at George Washington University, 1948.; Includes bibliographical references (leaves 1-2).
  - Eli Whitney by Charles Campbell., 1949-06-01; Series 11; iii, 30 leaves; 28 cm (Box 1, Folder 5)
    United Daughters of the Confederacy prize essay, 1949.; Includes bibliographical references (leaf 30).
  - A few notes on the contributions of Patrick Henry to the American Revolution by Joyce M. Wilson., 1949-06-01; Series 11; 18 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Society of the Colonial Dames of America, Chapter III, prize essay at George Washington University, 1949.; Includes bibliographical references (leaves 17-18).
  - The International Cooperation Year: An Analysis, 1966-06-01; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Our Father Who Art on Broadway, 1968; Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - William Molyneux and intellectual development in the late seventeenth-century Ireland by Sharon M. O'Connell., 1969-04-30; Series 11; 47 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Includes bibliographical references.; Thomas F. Walsh prize essay, 1969.
  - Hearing In RE: Violation of University Policies, 1969-05-14; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Germanic kingship ideas: the basis of royal power before the Carolingians by Analouise C. Bolten., 1970; Series 11; 41 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Typescript.; Charles Clinton Swisher Historical Club prize essay, 1970.; Contains bibliography.
  - The improvement of the Church of Ireland in the latter part of the reign of Elizabeth by D.L.C. Galles., 1970; Series 11; 30, [11] leaves; 27 cm. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Typescript (photocopy).; Thomas F. Walsh Prize in Irish History winner, 1970.; Contains bibliography.
  - Ritual Initiation in "Tiny Alice", 1970-04-18; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The influence of British Parliamentary legislation upon the changing pattern of Irish immigration into the United States between 1830 and 1840 by Charles Hill., 1971-10-01; Series 11; 123 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Thomas F. Walsh Prize in Irish History winner, 1972.; Typescript (photocopy).
  - The spread of the Sainte-Chapelle style: the building and its copies in France, England, and the Holy Roman Empire to the end of the Middle Ages by Margy P. Sharpe., 1972-03-23; Series 11; iii, 48, [3] leaves; 28 cm. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Charles Clinton Swisher Historical Club prize essay, 1972.; Contains bibliography.; Typescript (photocopy).
  - The Scottish undertakers and the Ulster plantation, 1609-1619 by Richard A. Pandich., 1974; Series 11; 29 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Typescript (carbon copy).; Thomas F. Walsh Prize in Irish History winner, 1974.; Contains bibliography.
  - Silk screen printed yardage utilizing traditional damask and brocade motifs by Aramide Omotayo Agbabiaka., 1982; Series 11; iv, 57 leaves: color illustrations; 28 cm (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Typescript.; M.F.A. George Washington University 1982; Includes bibliographical references (leaves 56-57).
  - Academic Evaluation Course Guide, Fall 1988; Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The value of the semantic differential to the art educator by Denise Wilkins., 2015; Series 11; 1 computer disc (v, 80 pages, 25 supplemental files): color illustrations; 4 3/4 in. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Submitted in partial fulfillment of the degree of Master of Arts.; Thesis (M.A.)--The George Washington University, 2015.; Includes bibliographical references (pages 63-65).; application/pdf; Text (PDF); Also available online.
- Labor, Series 12
  - Behavioral Phenomena Observed with Respect to the Implementation of Equal Employment Opportunity in the Veterans Administration, 1966-12-22; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A Chronic Surplus of College Graduates?, 1988; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A Demonstration Project to Prepare Selected College Graduates for Federal Employment, 1967-06-28; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Audio-Visual Presentation for Instruction of Federal Protective Officers, 1976-05-04; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Survey of Research on Job Satisfaction, 1973-06-06; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A Profile of Human Factor Requirements in the Maritime Industry, 1965-04-01; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Human Performance and Productivity: Pyschological Research in the Military, 1983; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fear and Courage: A Psychological Study, Undated; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - A Procedure for Forecasting the Size of a Force Subject to Random Withdrawal, 1975-06-24; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Principles and Hypotheses of Executive Leadership to Guide Executive Action, 1965-10-01; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Designing Job Loss Compensation Provisions: Lessons from the Airline Deregulation Experience, 1985; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Psychological Dimensions of Work: An Experimental Taxonomy of Occupations, 1964-12-01; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Federal Aid to Depressed Areas: An Experiment on Trial, 1963-09-01; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Workforce Statistics: Do We Know What We Think We Know--And What Should We Know?, 1989-11-01; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Burnout and the Social Service Professions: An Annotated Bibliography, 1980-05-01; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Job Adjustment and Employee Health, 1969-12-01; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Project '70: Projecting the State-Local Sector, 1966-03-09; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Encouraging Improved Planning in State and Local Government: The Federal Role, 1968-09-01; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Report on Project on State-Local Finances, 1970, 1965-06-01; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Effects of Time-Sharing and Body Positional Demands on Cutaneous Information Processing, 1965-07-01; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The George Washington University Rehabilitation Research and Training Center Annual Report, 1965; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The George Washington University Rehabilitation Research and Training Center Second Annual Report, 1966; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The George Washington University Rehabilitation Research and Training Center Progress Report, 1966-1967, 1967-10-15; Series 12 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The George Washington University Rehabilitation Research and Training Center Progress Report, 1967-1968, 1968-10-15; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The George Washington University Rehabilitation Research and Training Center Progress Report, 1968-1969, 1969-10-15; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The George Washington University Rehabilitation Research and Training Center Progress Report, 1969-1970, 1970-10-15; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The George Washington University Rehabilitation Research and Training Center Progress Report, 1970-1971, 1971-10-15; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The George Washington University Rehabilitation Research and Training Center Progress Report No. 8, 1971-1972; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The George Washington University Rehabilitation Research and Training Center Progress Report No. 9, 1972-1973; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The George Washington University Rehabilitation Research and Training Center 15th Annual Progress Report, 1979-1980; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Research Directory of the Rehabilitation Research and Training Centers: Fiscal Year 1970, 1971-02-01; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Research Directory of the Rehabilitation Research and Training Centers: Fiscal Year 1971, 1972-02-01; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Research Directory of the Rehabilitation Research and Training Centers: Fiscal Year 1972, 1973-02-01; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Research Directory of the Rehabilitation Research and Training Centers: Fiscal Year 1973, 1974-02-01; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Principles of Technical Assistance Consultation for Rehabilitation Personnel, 1981-02-01; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Putting Research to Use in Rehabilitation, 1980-02-19; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Rehabilitation Counselor-Client Study: Final Report, 1980-04-01; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Attitudes and Disability: A Selected Annotated Bibliography, January 1975 - August 1977; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Attitudes and Disability: A Selected Annotated Bibliography, 1975-1981, 1981-08-01; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Training and Evalution Program in the Utlization of Accessible Buses: Final Report, 1981-06-01; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Transit Information for the Handicapped: Final Report, 1983-12-01; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Disability Awareness: A Train-the-Trainer Manual, Undated; Series 12 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - A Study of the Effectiveness of Selected Out-of-School Neighborhood Youth Corps Programs; A Study of Terminated Enrollees in Three Urban Out-of-School Neighborhood Youth Corps Programs, 1963-05-01; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - GWU Manpower Research Project: A Study of the Effectiveness of Select Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1971-04-01; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sexuality and Disability: A Selected Annotated Bibliography, 1979; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Who Cares? A Handbook on Sex Education and Counseling Services for Disabled People, 1979; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - A Survey of State Officials: Current and Future Development of Intermiediate Care Facilities for the Mentally Retarded, 1980-08-01; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - A Proposal for a National Demonstration Special Report on Mental Retardation: The Re-Education of American Society, 1976-04-16; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - A Listing of Disability-Oriented Consumer &amp Support Organizations, Undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Rehabilitation Research and Training Center: Job Placement for People with Severe Disabilities, 1978-03-01; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Use of Systems Analysis in Vocational Rehabilitation Research, 1969-06-01; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Handbook of Employment Rights of the Handicapped: Sections 503 and 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, 1978; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Accomodating the Disabled Student, Undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Designing for Functional Limitations, Undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - A Longitudinal Study of Selected Out-of-School NYC-2 Programs in Four Cities: Report of Phase I, 1970-11-01; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - A Longitudinal Study of Selected Out-of-School NYC-2 Programs in Four Cities: Report of Phase II, 1972-02-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - A Longitudinal Study of Selected Out-of-School Neighborhood Youth Corps Programs: Implications for Program Operations and Research, 1969-02-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - A Study of Terminated Enrollees in Three Urban Out-of-school Neighborhood Youth Corps Programs, 1969-02-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - A Longitudinal Study of Selected Out-of-school NYC-2 Programs in Four Cities: Final Report, 1975-06-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - A Retrospective Study of the Effectiveness of Out-of-school Neighborhood Youth Corps Programs in Four Urban Sites, 1967-11-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - A Study of the Effectiveness of Selected Out-of-school Neighborhood Youth Corps Programs: The Accelerated Learning Experiment. Progress Report, 1968-04-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - A Study of the Effectiveness of Selected Out-of-school Neighborhood Youth Corps Programs: The Accelerated Learning Experiment. Second Progress Report, 1968-09-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - A Study of the Effectiveness of Selected Out-of-school Neighborhood Youth Corps Programs: Methodological Considerations in Evaluative Research Involving Disadvantaged Populations, 1968-05-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Cincinnati Clerical Co-op: A Formal Skill Training Program, 1969; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - A Retrospective Study of the Effectiveness of the Cincinnati Out-of-school Neighborhood Youth Corps Program, 1967-07-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - A Study of the Effectiveness of Selected Out-of-school Neighborhood Youth Corps Programs: The Measurement of Work-Relevant Attitudes, 1969-02-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - A Study of the Effectiveness of the Graham Associates' Demonstration Project on NYC-2 Education Programming: Progress Report No. 2, 1972-09-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - A Study of the Effectiveness of the Graham Associates' Demonstration Project on NYC-2 Education Programming: Final Report, 1973-08-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - A Study of the Effectiveness of the Graham Associates' Demonstration Project on Education Programming in Manpower Training Projects: Report No. 2, the First Months, 1974-04-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - The Measurement of Work-relevant Attitudes: A Report on the Development of a Measuring Instrument, 1970-07-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - The Measurement of Work-relevant Attitudes: A Report on the Development of a Measuring Instrument. Final Report, 1970-10-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - The Measurement of Work-relevant Attitudes, 1972-09-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - The Supply of Young Craftsmen to an Industry, 1980-06-12; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Social and Educational Antecedents to Youth Unemployment, 1979-08-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Intense Employment While in High School: Are Teachers, Guidance Counselors, and Parents Misguiding Academically-Oriened Adolescents, 1987; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Work Experience as Preparation for Adulthood: A Review of Federal Job Training, Vocational, and Career Education Programs, An Analysis of Current Research, and Recommendations for Future Research, 1973-05-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - An Evaluation of the 1972 Washington Summer Intern Program of the Department of Labor, 1973-08-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Uncle Sam's Helping Hand: Educating, Training, and Employing the Disadvantaged, 1989; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - On the Use of Applicant Flow Data in Establishing Fair Employment Standards, 1976-03-24; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Part-time Employment: Living on Half-rations, 1988; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - The Working Poor: A Missing Element in Welfare Reform, 1987; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - The Financial Incentive Offered by Low-wage Jobs to Receipients of Income Support Benefits, 1988; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - The Washington Labor Force: As Asset in a Changing Economy, 1985-01-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Emerging Employment Patterns in the Washington Area and its Jurisdictions: 1967-1977 and 1977-1982, 1984-12-01; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Employment and Training Activities Serving Predominantly Low-income Residents of Washington, D.C., with Limited Employment Qualifications, 1988; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Employment Opportunities in the Washington Metropolitan Area for Persons with Limited Employment Qualifications, 1988; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - The Hardship Consequences of Labor Market Problems, 1982-06-17; Series 12 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - The Unnaturally Inflated Rate of Unemployment, 1986; Series 12 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings Conference on Effective Measures of Emergency Unemployment Relief at G.W.U., 1932-07-01; Series 12 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Workbook: Developing New Horizons for Women; Career Development for Employed Women, 1974; Series 12 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Manual, A Counselor's Guide for the Workbook: Developing New Horizons for Women; Career Development for Employed Women, 1975; Series 12 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - More Women Working: The Growth of Washington's Female Labor Force, 1960 to 1979, 1981-09-01; Series 12 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Manual, A Counselor's Guide for the Workbook: Developing New Horizons for Women; Career Development for Employed Women, 1975; Series 12 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Developing New Horizons for Women Workbook, 1971; Series 12 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Special Report: Greater Washington's Labor Shortage, 1932; Series 12 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Communications Resources, Series 13
  - Television News Resources: A Guide to Collections, Undated; Series 13; 27 pages; 28 cm (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Economic Theory in Industrial Policy: Lessons From U.S. v. AT&T, 1989; Series 13; 32 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Telecommunications Policy: A Survey Bibliography, 1983-07-01; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mass Communication and Electronic Media: A Survey Bibliography, 1983-07-01; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Foreign and International Communications Systems: A Survey Bibliography, 1983-10-01; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Videoconferencing Via Satellite: Opening Congress to the People, 1978-02-01; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Strategies for the Use of Communications Media in the Technologically Developing Nations (Vol. 1), 1973; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Strategies for the Use of Communications Media in the Technologically Developing Nations (Vol. 2), 1973; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Mass Communications Media in the Developing Nations: Source Compilation Report, 1971-07-20; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Communications Explosion: The Role of Communciations Technology in Democracy; On the Effects of Communications Satellites, 1965-06-01; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Computers, Television, and Privacy: Merging Technologies, Emerging Threats?, 1980-01-01; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - USPS and the Communications Revolution: Impacts, Options, and Issues, 1977-03-05; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Future of the Network Concept, 1966-01-01; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Organizational Cybernetics and Human Values, 1969-09-01; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Influence of Insurance on Technological Development, 1969-11-01; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Broadcast Satellites: Their Potential Use for Educational Purposes, and Their Relationship to International Understanding and Cooperation, 1969-07-01; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - World-wide Television and the National Interest: A Preliminary Inquiry, 1965-02-01; Series 13 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- The Arts and Museums and Dance, Series 14
  - Maida Withers: "Light Suite," "Rings," "Dunes," and "Wall Floating", 1986-1987; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Maida Withers: "Obsession," Dance and Interview, 1987; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Maida Withers: "Orbit", 1990; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Danceworks Spring 2017, 2016-2017; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Information About Information: An Annotated Bibliography, January 1, 1977; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Information About Information: An Annotated Bibliography (Vol. 1), January 1, 1977; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Information About Information: An Annotated Bibliography (Vol. 2), April 1, 1978; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Museum and the Art Teacher, December 1966; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Smithsonian Visitor Study: Assessing the Need for a Secondary Transit System, 1980; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Smithsonian: Enhancing the Visitor's Experience, May 1984; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Once Upon a Time: A Celebration of the Life and Work of Diane Bell, June 8, 2005; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Unraveling: Senior Thesis Work, 2021 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Scope and Contents
    Fulfilling the BFA in Photojournalism, senior thesis work from the class of 2021 in the Corcoran School of Arts and Design.
  - If the Sky Falls and Universal Uncertainty, 2020-2021 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Publications of photograph from the School of Photojournalism, in the Corcoran School of Arts and Design. Some of these photos were taken during quarantine of the covid-19 pandemic.
- Population Studies, Series 15
  - Analysis of Traffic Circulation of The George Washington University Campus, April 1974; Series 15 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Space Program and the Urban Problem: Case Studies of the Components of National Consensus, 1969.; Series 15 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Linkages Between Small Metropolitan Places Areas and Their Hinterlands with Implications for Regional Development Policies, May 1972; Series 15 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Leesburg: A Growth Study, 1970; Series 15 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Inventory and Appraisal of University Activities in Urban Social/Minority Group Problem Areas, May 20, 1968; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Urban Development Modeling, April 1970; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Old Orchard Beach, ME: Planning Study of a Resort Community, June 1968; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Boyds Maryland: A Planning Study, June 1971; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Mount Vernon Square Study Area: A Research Study, January 1971; Series 15 (Box 2, Folder 5)